<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="hero_name">You</string>
    <string name="school_friend_name">Student</string>
    <string name="school_master_name">School Master</string>
    <string name="officer_name">Army Recruiter</string>
    <string name="counselor_name">King\'s Counselor</string>
    <string name="king_name">King of Erya</string>
    <string name="priest_name">High Priest</string>

    <string-array name="level_stories">
        <!-- One levels is always composed of 3 items: enemy name, start story and end story
             Format is always "speaker_name@LeftOrRight:sentence" and a "\n" is needed to separate sentences
             Item can be empty -->

        <!-- Level 1 to 10 -->
        <item>school_friend</item>
        <item>school_friend@R:So, finally you\'ll get graduated tomorrow!\n
            school_friend@R:Are you stressed by the final examination?\n
            hero@L:Well, not really.\n
            hero@L:I don\'t expect the examination to be that hard. This invoker school is not famous for its difficulty.\n
            school_friend@R:Sure, that\'s why I selected that one!\n
            school_friend@R:But still, what about a small training fight?\n
            hero@L:I don\'t really need to, you know?\n
            school_friend@R:Oh, come on! I\'ll start gently with a small card.\n
            school_friend@R:And I\'m really curious to see what kind of creatures you can invoke now.\n
            hero@L:If you insist…</item>
        <item>school_friend@R:Well, I knew you would have defeated that one easily.\n
            hero@L:Is that all you can do?\n
            school_friend@R:Don\'t worry, the next one will be stronger!\n
            school_friend@R:If I were you I would get some new cards at the school library.\n
            school_friend@R:I heard that the owner was once a great invoker but now he is starting to get too old for that and
            trade his invoker cards in exchange of some well-executed _tasks.\n
            school_friend@R:That\'s a easy way to become a better invoker, but be careful: you can\'t take too many card in your
            deck unless you become more experienced and gain more free slots.</item>

        <item>school_friend</item>
        <item>school_friend@R:So, ready to fight?\n
            hero@L:I don\'t need to be ready to defeat you.</item>
        <item>school_friend@R:Again, it seems to be so easy for you that it\'s almost frustrating…\n
            school_friend@R:But it\'s not finished yet, I still have something to try.\n
            school_friend@R:I have some support card to use after my creatures to reinforce them, so you would better prepare
            yourself.</item>

        <item>school_friend</item>
        <item>school_friend@R:Now I\'ll go full power! Prepare yourself!\n
            hero@L:How long will that last? I\'m not in the mood of playing.</item>
        <item>school_friend@R:Well, I admit there is no use to continue, I guess you\'re ready for the examination.\n
            school_friend@R:More you level up and more you\'ll be able to easily invoke several powerful creatures, I have to
            admit I\'m curious to see how far you\'ll end up in the army.\n
            school_friend@R:By the way, do you already knows what you want to do after your diploma?\n
            hero@L:Yes. However it is a bit complicated to explain.\n
            school_friend@R:Huh? OK, anyway the Erya Kingdom is recruiting almost everyone for his army, so I guess you won\'t have much
            choice actually.</item>

        <item>school_master</item>
        <item>school_master@R:Here is the final examination day!\n
            school_master@R:How do you feel?\n
            hero@L:As usual, ready.\n
            school_master@R:Great. You just have to win that battle and you\'ll be an official Erya Kingdom invoker!</item>
        <item>school_master@R:Here you are! That wasn\'t hard for you, right?\n
            school_master@R:I\'m happy to say you\'re now an official invoker, you\'ll soon receive your diploma.\n
            school_master@R:Afterward you\'ll be interviewed by an Erya Kingdom officer. The kingdom is trying to reinforce his army and
            they integrate a lot of students.</item>

        <item>officer</item>
        <item>officer@R:So before we start let me present myself: I was also an invoker student and I\'m now lieutenant in the Erya army.\n
            officer@R:I\'m notably in charge of recruiting invokers from all over the kingdom and assign them to a specific regiment.\n
            officer@R:First of all, show me what you are capable of.</item>
        <item />

        <item>officer</item>
        <item>officer@R:I have to say I\'m impressed. You have your place in our great army.\n
            hero@L:I don\'t want to integrate the army.\n
            officer@R:Well, I\'m afraid you cannot really refuse the proposition. The King orders are clears, we need to requisitioned all
            capable people.\n
            officer@R:If you refuse you risk to be judge for disloyalty.\n
            hero@L:Fine. But before bring me to the King\'s counselor. Even if I don\'t integrate the army, I can be very useful to the King.\n
            hero@L:I have some information that will interest the King, and I can do more than what you have seen for now.\n
            hero@L:Let me prove it to you right now with a second fight, but this time do not restrain yourself.</item>
        <item>officer@R:I see… You\'re clearly above the level of a classic newly graduated invoker.\n
            hero@L:Now please bring me to the counselor. I have a proposal that he will like.\n
            officer@R:OK, let\'s go to the King\'s Castle. But don\'t be too optimistic, I\'ll closely watch you and there is big chances he will
            not accept to receive you.</item>

        <item>counselor</item>
        <item>officer@R:You\'re lucky, the counselor accepted to see you, but he wants to know your motivations.\n
            counselor@R:Exactly. Be strong is not a good enough reason to see the King, what do you want exactly?\n
            hero@L:I came from the forest village of Oras.\n
            hero@L:The life was peaceful there, however the river is almost dried now. So the forest is dying and the village with it.\n
            officer@R:Could it be…\n
            hero@L:Yes. It is due to the fact that the King had rerouted the river for the army needs.\n
            counselor@R:So you are here for revenge? The whole continent is in need of water and we unfortunately have to do some choices.\n
            hero@L:I know the situation. I also know that the recent tensions between us, the Myrth Kingdom and the Qahor Kingdom are due to the water.\n
            hero@L:But I have a solution and a deal.\n
            counselor@R:And what would that be?\n
            hero@L:I cannot speak here with so many people around. I request an interview with the King.\n
            counselor@R:Our majesty is well occupied, as you can imagined. I\'m sorry but this is out of question.\n
            counselor@R:Guards, please escort this young women outside.\n
            hero@L:Wait!</item>
        <item>counselor@R:Why are you opposing resistance? I could execute you for that, and what tells me that you do not want to harm our Majesty?\n
            hero@L:It is really important for me to see the King, and killing him will not save my village.\n
            counselor@R:Well… You\'ll first explain your plan to me in privacy. Then I may change my mind.</item>

        <item>king</item>
        <item>counselor@R:So, please describe me that plan of you.\n
            hero@L:Well, it\'s…\n
            king@R:Sorry to interrupt, Counselor, I would need your help in the war room. Please call everyone.\n
            counselor@R:Majesty, I were actually interviewing this girl who pretends to have a solution for our problem, it\'s maybe good to listen
            to her before doing that meeting.\n
            king@R:Well, young girl, if my counselor says so, you can speak.\n
            hero@L:Sir, I came here to propose a deal.\n
            hero@L:Let me start a war between Myrth and Qahor. In exchange I ask to stop drying up the Oras\'s river.\n
            king@R:Start a war between Myrth and Qahor? Why would I want that?\n
            hero@L:Because Myrth knows that they will not win without your help. If we ally with them, we can defeat Qahor and share their lands.\n
            hero@L:We could notably obtain the Great Mountains, including their water sources, which should solve our water issues.\n
            hero@L:Moreover, today Myrth and Qahor are allies. When they will run out of water as well, they will certainly think of a similar plan against us.
            It\'s maybe already the case, we need to reverse the trend.\n
            counselor@R:Surprisingly, you may be quite close to the reality. Our Majesty and myself just learned that Myrth and Qahor\'s Kings started to meet
            each other quite a lot theses days, I don\'t think it\'s positive for us.\n
            king@R:Well, young girl, I like your analyse. But tell me: how do you plan to start that war?\n
            hero@L:I don\'t think it is hard, humans can be easily manipulated.\n
            hero@L:My invoking capabilities are a bit different than usual: I can invoke creatures at a very long distances and during a long period. I could
            go to Myrth and invoke some false Qahor\'s soldiers inside the King\'s castle to assassinate the King.\n
            hero@L:If my invocations succeed to kill the King, the Myrth\'s Prince will believe that Qahor is behing that and will declare war to them.\n
            hero@L:If my invocations fail, the Myrth\'s King will start the war himself.\n
            hero@L:In all cases we reach our goals.\n
            king@R:…\n
            king@R:This could work, but it is all based on your supposed invoking capabilities.\n
            king@R:Let test them with some guards of mine.</item>
        <item>king@R:…\n
            king@R:I start to be convinced. But I can\'t trust you yet. Moreover I have no guarantee that you are actually capable of killing an innocent man.\n
            hero@L:A king is never really innocent.\n
            king@R:Hahaha! You\'re courageous to dare saying that in front of me!\n
            king@R:But that\'s not wrong actually. I start to like you, little girl.\n
            king@R:Counselor, please continue to investigate that proposal. Meanwhile, find a way to be sure she is really capable of it.</item>

        <item>priest</item>
        <item>counselor@R:I found you a task to prove your efficiency. I would like you to kill the High Priest of the city and make it looks like a robbery.\n
            counselor@R:If you succeed in it we will accept your deal. If you fail, we will execute you for tentative of assassination on a representative of God.\n
            hero@L:What did this man do to deserve that?\n
            counselor@R:You\'ll know if you return.\n
            story:The evening, in the church…\n
            priest@R:Who are you? What are you doing here at this hour?\n
            hero@L:I am officially a thief, but in reality I\'m here to assassinate you.\n
            hero@L:Your death is part of a very big plan. Maybe your God actually approves it.\n
            priest@R:What? This church is surrounded by guards, I just have to call them and you\'ll be the one to die!\n
            hero@L:Please do. I\'ll let you with my invocations now, and they need some witnesses of their \"robbery\".\n
            priest@R:Wh…? GUARDS!</item>
        <item>story:The day after, at the King\'s castle…\n
            counselor@R:I heard that your mission was a success, some soldiers survived and declared that it was a thieves attack. I start to believe you are really
            capable of what you proposed.\n
            counselor@R:Do you want to know why I gave you that mission?\n
            hero@L:From that priest point of view I\'m sure it does not really matter anymore.\n
            counselor@R:You are a strange girl, you know?\n
            counselor@R:Anyway, the reason of that mission was quite simple actually. This high priest started to spread some negative words against our King, and we believe
            this could start a revolt.\n
            hero@L:So you just wanted to protect the King?\n
            counselor@R:Our King appreciates the religion, but only when it legitimates his reign. It is true that he was not in love anymore with that priest.\n
            counselor@R:However he did not ask me to kill him, and I did not do it for him. I actually think some arguments of that priest were valid, but I had to make
            him silent to protect the country.\n
            counselor@R:We will soon enter in war, if we go through a revolt now we will have to split our forces and will certainly suffer a quick invasion from our neighbours.\n
            counselor@R:I believe nobody wants that, including the people and the priests. What seems to be an odious act can sometimes be something needed.\n
            hero@L:I understand.</item>

    </string-array>

</resources>
