<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<resources>
    <string-array name="level_stories">
        <!-- One levels is always composed of 3 items: enemy name, start story and end story
             Format is always "speaker_name@LeftOrRight:sentence" and a "\n" is needed to separate sentences
             Item can be empty -->

        <!-- Level 1 to 10 -->
        <item>school_friend</item>
        <item>school_friend@R:So, finally you\'ll get graduated tomorrow!\n
            school_friend@R:Are you stressed by the final examination?\n
            hero@L:Well, not really.\n
            hero@L:I don\'t expect the examination to be that hard. This invoker school is not famous for its difficulty.\n
            school_friend@R:Sure, that\'s why I selected that one!\n
            school_friend@R:But still, what about a small training fight?\n
            hero@L:I don\'t really need to, you know?\n
            school_friend@R:Oh, come on! I\'ll start gently with a small card.\n
            school_friend@R:And I\'m really curious to see what kind of creatures you can invoke now.\n
            hero@L:If you insist…</item>
        <item>school_friend@R:Well, I knew you would have defeated that one easily.\n
            hero@L:Is that all you can do?\n
            school_friend@R:Don\'t worry, the next one will be stronger!\n
            school_friend@R:If I were you I would get some new cards at the school library.\n
            school_friend@R:I heard that the owner was once a great invoker but now he is starting to get too old for that and
            trade his invoker cards in exchange of some well-executed tasks.\n
            school_friend@R:Then look at needed mana slots in the top-right corner of the cards and compose the best deck you can!</item>

        <item>school_friend</item>
        <item>school_friend@R:So, ready to fight?\n
            hero@L:I don\'t need to be ready to defeat you.</item>
        <item>school_friend@R:Again, it seems to be so easy for you that it\'s almost frustrating…\n
            school_friend@R:But it\'s not finished yet, I still have something to try.\n
            school_friend@R:I have some support card to use after my creatures to reinforce them, so you would better prepare yourself.</item>

        <item>school_friend</item>
        <item>school_friend@R:Now I\'ll go full power! Prepare yourself!\n
            hero@L:How long will that last? I\'m not in the mood of playing.</item>
        <item>school_friend@R:Well, I admit there is no use to continue, I guess you\'re ready for the examination.\n
            school_friend@R:More you level up and more you\'ll be able to easily invoke several powerful creatures, I have to admit I\'m curious to see see how far you\'ll end up in the army.\n
            school_friend@R:By the way, do you already knows what you\'ll do after your diploma?\n
            hero@L:Do I really have the choice?\n
            school_friend@R:It\'s true that the Arya Kingdom is recruiting almost everyone for his army, but there is several possibilities for an invoker inside the army.\n
            school_friend@R:Some decide to help with construction and some prefer to fight.\n
            hero@L:In all cases women are not allowed to fight, they can only support the army. So the choice is quite limited.</item>

        <item>school_master</item>
        <item>school_master@R:Here is the final examination day!\n
            school_master@R:How do you feel?\n
            hero@L:Ready to pass it.\n
            school_master@R:Great. You just have to win that battle and you\'ll be an official Arya Kingdom invoker!</item>
        <item>school_master@R:Great! That wasn\'t hard, right? I\'m happy to say you\'re now a real invoker!</item>

    </string-array>

</resources>
